WILLIAM GEHRKE

Middlesex, NJ 08846 | 732-556-7870 | WilliamEGehrke@gmail.com | WillGehrke.com

Full Stack Web Developer

As a web developer with a background in human services, I bring a unique perspective to the field. My experience working with diverse communities has given me an in-depth understanding of the needs of different users, which is vital in creating user-friendly and accessible websites. My background in human services has also taught me the importance of clear communication and attention to detail - all of which are critical skills I bring to my work in web development.

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript

- React.is
- React MUI
- MongoDB

- MySQL
- GraphQL
- Express.js

Software Development

MovieSwipe

Fullstack MERN application that allows users to save their favorite movies through swiper interaction

StreamingSearch

Node application using API calls to search movie and TV shows current streaming platforms

CodeABreak

Express and Node application that allows users to share resources for coding

Work Experience

Freelance Web Developer

2022 to Present

- · Handling all verbal and written communications between clients and companies.
- Designing, developing and maintaining websites for projects using HTML, CSS, Javascript and other languages as needed.
- · Collaborate with consumers to implement periodic updates to websites.

Peer Support Specialist

2020 to 2022

Rutgers UBHC

Monmouth Junction, NJ

- · Linked and assisted consumers with resources while using decision making strategies to find appropriate services
- Maintained and tracked consumer progress using efficient workflow practices utilizing the electronic medical record system

Treatment Associate

2018 to 2020

New Hope Integrated Behavioral Health

Marlboro, NJ

- Coordinated all daily activities of 60+ clients to appropriate substance abuse counselors
- Led treatment groups and therapeutic activities on functional living skills and addressing behavioral issues

Education and Training

Associate of Science: Human Services/Pre-Social Work

10/2022

Raritan Valley Community College, Branchburg , $\ensuremath{\mathsf{NJ}}$

Rutgers Coding Bootcamp

10/2022

Rutgers University, New Brunswick, NJ

Volunteer Experience

All Hands and Hearts

2019

Disaster Relief Response

Pride Center of New Jersey

Front Desk Host/Youth Drop In

St. Thomas, US Virgin Islands & Bayboro, North Carolina 2019-2022

Highland Park, NJ